com.ibm.uk.hursley.perfharness.Log:
Sets up JDK 1.4+ logging for the application.

  st	Print full stack trace on error. (default: true)
  vo	Verbosity level for logging.  Messages below this level will not be logged. (default: INFO)
	This must be parsable by java.util.logging.Level.parse().

com.ibm.uk.hursley.perfharness.Config:
Centralises parsing, access and reporting of configuration parameters.

  hx	Display help as XML. (default: false)
  hs	Strict configuration checking. (default: true)
	If true, this enables strict registration and checking of all
	application parameters.
  hm	Display detailed help on a specific module or modules. (default: )
	Specify multiple modules as space-separated tokens.
	Example: -hm "WebSphereMQ WBIMB"
  hf	Display detailed help on current configuration. (default: false)
  v	Show version. (default: false)
  hp	Config properties filename. (default: )
	Any values on the commandline take precedence over the contents of this file.
  h	Display basic help on current configuration. (default: false)

com.ibm.uk.hursley.perfharness.ControlThread:
Manage the lifecycle of the application and any WorkerThreads.


  so	Starts a socket shutdown thread on port specified (default: 0)
	Starts thread listening on the port specified, if zero no thread started.
	Once thread receives any data on socket a shutdown is signalled.
  rl	Run length in seconds. (default: 60)
	Setting this to 0 will disable the timer and run forever.
  wi	WorkerThread start interval (ms). (default: 1000)
	This controls the pause between starting multiple threads.
  su	Display final summary. (default: true)
	This setting is independent of the periodic statistics reporting.
  wt	WorkerThread start timeout (s). (default: 30)
	This controls the time to wait for any worker thread to start.
  nt	Number of WorkerThreads. (default: 1)
  id	Process identifier. (default: )
	If set, this will be displayed in the statistics reporting.  This is
	of use if you have to merge the output of more than one instance of the tool.
  wk	Shutdown wait (s). (default: 120)
	The application will wait this long for WorkerThreads to shutdown before
	exiting anyway.
  ct	ControlThread instance to invoke in this application. (default: ControlThread)
  sh	Use signal handler to trap SIGINT (CTRL-C). (default: true)

com.ibm.uk.hursley.perfharness.WorkerThread:
Base class for all varieties of test.  This class implements a general pacing
algorithm for those tests that wish to use it.  The performance overhead of this
is minimal.

  rp	Time period (s) to ramp up to the full rate. (default: 0)
  df	Destination factory implementation. (default: DefaultDestinationFactory)
	Currently, there is only one option.
		DefaultDestinationFactory
  mg	Fixed number of iterations to run. (default: 0)
	The default setting of 0 means there is no iteration limit.
  ln	Use a logarithmic distribution to "randomise" a fixed rate.  (default: false)
  tc	Test definition class. (default: jms.r11.PutGet)
	This defines the actual type of WorkerThreads that will be
	started.  The selections listed are those packaged with this tool, there
	may be others on the classpath that will not be shown here.
		jms.r11.PutGet
		jms.r11.Sender
		jms.r11.Receiver
		jms.r11.Requestor
		jms.r11.Responder
		jms.r11.Publisher
		jms.r11.Subscriber
		mqjava.PutGet
		mqjava.Sender
		mqjava.Receiver
		mqjava.Requestor
		mqjava.Responder
  yd	Frequency to call Thread.yield(). (default: 0)
	This may be of use if the WorkerThreads are not being evenly scheduled.
	Note that enforcing fairness will impact overall performance.
  rt	Desired rate (operations/sec). (default: 0)
	If this rate is greater than the maximum achievable, the behaviour
	is such that it runs as fast as possible.  A value of 0 means to
	always run as fast as possible.  Rates of <1 op/sec are not currently possible.

com.ibm.uk.hursley.perfharness.mqjava.Requestor:
Puts a message to a queue then waits for a reply on another queue.  In contrast to the JMS
classes, a new correlation-id is used for every request if -co is specified.

  iq	Queue to place requests on. (default: REQUEST)
  mm	New MQMessage object (default: 0)
	If this value is >0 then for each MQ get a new MQMessage object is instantiated
  wo	Number of messages sent before a reponse message is written to a file (default: 0)
	If this value is >0 then each client thread will write a response
	message to a file in the current dir called threadname.reponsemsg
  oq	Queue to place replies on. (default: REPLY)
  mdm	Minimum numeric value to be appended to multi-destination queue names (default: 2)
	If a multi-destination index is less than this value, then it will
	not be appended to the input/output queue names. I.e., if this value is set to
	2 and the multi-destination numbering goes from 1 to 3, then the actual queue
	names used will be <inputqueue>, <outputqueue>, <intputqueue>2, <outputqueue>2,
	<inputqueue>3, <outputqueue>3. If the value 1 is used for the same numbering,
	the first pair of queues used will be <inputqueue>1 and <outputqueue>1.
  qm	Reply to  QueueManager to put messages to, replies will be local. (default: )

com.ibm.uk.hursley.perfharness.mqjava.MQProvider:
Provides access to WebSphere MQ classes for Java

  jh	Host to connect to. (default: localhost)
  tx	Transactionality. (default: false)
  me	MQ Message Encoding.  This value is set on the MQ Message in the MQMessage.encodingfield field. (default: 546)
  pp	Use persistent messages. (default: false)
  to	Polling timeout on receiving messages (0 means forever). (default: 5)
	Threads will not stop if this timeout occurs, it simply the polling interval.
	Note that when using a value of 0, the tool probably won't exit cleanly.
  bf	Force MQOO_BIND_NOT_FIXED for clusters. (default: false)
	This is normally done by changing the queue definition to DEFBIND(NOTFIXED).
  ir	input to out put ratio, default =1  e.g. 3 means send 3 then get 1. (default: 1)
  or	output to input ratio, default =1  e.g. 3 means put 1 then get 3 msgs, can used for pubsub fan out. (default: 1)
  jc	WMQ Channel to connect to. (default: SYSTEM.DEF.SVRCONN)
  jp	Port to connect to. (default: 1414)
  co	Use correlation-id on requests. (default: false)
	This will use the correlation-id per message model (unlike the JMS classes in this tool).
  ms	Message size in bytes. (default: 1000)
  mi	Use msg-id on requests. (default: false)
	This will use the msg-id received by the put() on the get() on a per thread basis.
  ws	Write last response message to the screen on shutdown (default: 0)
	If this value is >0 then each client thread will write the last response message received to the screen on shutdown.
  mq	MQ message format. This value is set on the MQ Message in the MQMessage.format field. (default: MQSTR)
	The value set should be the actual string that is the constant in the MQC.MQFMT* class, 
	 For example to specify MQC.MQFMT_TRIGGER then set -mq MQTRIG  
  jt	WMQ transport (mqb, mqbf, mqc). (default: mqc)
	"mqb" is local-bindings connections, "mqbf" is local fastpath connections,
	"mqc" is TCP/IP connections.
  rf	Use RFH Header from msg file, as produced by RFHUtil.  (default: 0)
	"rf" value of 1 means read as RFH1 header (MQC.MQFMT_RF_HEADER_1), 
	Value of 2 means RFH2 header (MQC.MQFMT_RF_HEADER_2).
  cv	Correlation ID value. (default: )
  mc	MQ Message Character Set.  This value is set on the MQ Message in the MQMessage.characterSet field. (default: 1208)
  jl	SSLCipherSuite name (default: )
	This controls the SSL encryption methodology.  RTFM or developerWorks for details.
  mf	External file to use as message contents. (default: )
  jb	WMQ queue manager to connect to. (default: QM)

com.ibm.uk.hursley.perfharness.DefaultDestinationFactory:
Defines the allocation of destinations amongst multiple WorkerThreads.
These options only control the *names* given to destination and it is up
to the WorkerThread implementation how these names are interpreted.

  db	Multi-destination numeric base. (default: 0)
  dx	Multi-destination numeric maximum. (default: 0)
  dn	Multi-destination numeric range. (default: 0)
	If both base and maximum are set, this value is taken to be the starting
	point (as opposed to base).
  d	Destination prefix. (default: DEST)
	If no other destination parameters are set, then nothing will be appended to this.

com.ibm.uk.hursley.perfharness.stats.Statistics:
  ss	Statistics reporting period. (default: 10)
	Setting this to 0 will disable periodic reporting entirely.
  sp	Display per-thread iteration counts. (default: false)
	The infomation given per thread is the number of iterations (not a
	rate/sec) in the reporting period.
  sw	Statistical discard period (seconds). (default: 0)
	The given warmup period is excluded from the calculations of
	final summary.
  sc	Statistics module to use - options are BasicStats, ResponseTimeStats or RollingAvgStats. (default: RollingAvgStats)
	
  sd	Sets what is reported as totalDuration. (default: normal)
	"normal" = from 1st iteration to last iteration, excluding setup/takedown.
	"tlf" = Time to Last Fire, from start of main thread till last iteration completes
	(includes setup time but not takedown).

com.ibm.uk.hursley.perfharness.stats.RollingAvgStats:
  sr	Rolling average period (seconds). (default: 30)
	Performance is sampled every second, the number reported is the
	average over the last rolling average period.  During the first period, the
	figure reported is the average over the actual number of seconds elapsed. 


